bigmuscle.com 2005-04-03

# Privacy

**1\. Under age visitors   to this site:**  
No one under twenty-one years of age is eligible to subscribe to, view or request products and/services via this website. We ask that under age visitors not view or submit information to us.

 **2\. Our Use of Your Information**  
We internally use personally identifiable information of our users to improve our marketing efforts, analyze site usage, improve our content and product offerings as well as to customize our site's content and layout. 

We may also use personally identifiable information about you to deliver information to you that, in some cases, are targeted to your interests, such as targeted banners and promotions. 

We also send periodic informational updates to our members via email. 

We use personally identifiable information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our User Agreement.

 **3\. Information We Collect**  
BigMuscle.com is an online website which provides you tools to communicate with others online. Our service is FREE to all qualified members. 

We ask you to provide us with certain information such as your birth date and email address, we use to forward your account login password. In addition, we can collect address, credit card, and bank information only from those who wish to acquire privileges or purchase goods and services offered via this website. 

In the course of using our site, we automatically track certain information such as your IP addresses, website pages accessed and e-mail addresses. Many sites automatically collect this information. If you choose to post messages in forums, chat rooms or other message areas, we will only display such information about you as you choose to reveal. 

If you send us correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the site, we may collect such information into a file, which is only accessed by authorized personnel or law enforcement officials on demand.

We also collect information about our users via Internet browser "Cookies".  If you choose not to enable and accept Cookies from our site, you user experience maybe degraded.

 **4\. Our Disclosure of Your Information**  
We DO NOT sell or rent any personally identifiable information about you to any third party without your permission. We do disclose information in aggregate to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we DO NOT disclose to these entities any information that could be used to personally identify you. Certain information, such as your password, credit card number, and bank account number, are not disclosed in aggregate at all. 

BigMuscle.com cooperates with all law enforcement inquiries and with all third parties to enforce their intellectual property or other rights.

 **5\. Your use of Other Users' Information**  
BigMuscle.com and our users do not tolerate spam, harassment, or threats. We retain the right to terminate without advance notice, any user or account that we find is spamming, harassing or threatening anyone, via this website. 

**6\. Control of Your Password**  
You may not disclose your password to any third parties or share it with any third parties. If, despite the foregoing, you lose control of your password, you may lose substantial control over your personally identifiable information and may be subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. Therefore, if your password has been compromised for any reason, you should immediately change your password.  

 **7.Third Party Collections of Information**  
BigMuscle.com has no control over any persons, third party web sites, link or email addresses posted to this website by users. Any web navigation that take you off this site, is not under our control.

 **8\. You Safety Is Important**  
We strongly suggest to you that you do not disclose any personal, financial or location (home, business or hotel) address information while on this site or while using the Internet at anytime. 

The Federal Trade Commission offers information about [surfing the Internet safely](http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/alerts/dialupalt.htm).

 **9\. Contact**   
To contact us please refer to our contact information. 

**10\. Private Information:**

AB Software disclaims all liability, regardless of the form of action, for the acts or omissions of other Members or users (including unauthorized users, or "hackers") of the Service. 

**11\. Change Privacy Statement:**

AB Software reserves the right to change our Privacy Policy without prior notice to anyone.

 **12\. Privacy Information:**

AB Software reserves the right to transfer ownership of all private and non private information collect from use of this web site to pending parties who may contract with AB Software to purchase controlling interest/partnership or full ownership of this web site.
